(upbeat music)
Congratulations on finishing
the introduction to JavaScript.
So you mastered the absolute fundamentals,
but there is still a lot of content ahead.
In fact, there is over 50 hours of video left
in this course.
However, I know that this is way too much for some people.
And so let's not take five or 10 minutes
to plan your unique journey through this course,
so that you can achieve your own learning goals.
Now to start, keep in mind that this is after all
the complete JavaScript course.
And so it makes sense that it covers everything,
and has a lot of big projects and challenges.
That's the reason why this course is so long.
But here is the thing,
you don't need to watch the entire course
to become really good at JavaScript.
There are many lectures and some sections
that you can safely skip and still become a great developer.
Now watching the entire course,
is, of course, the best option.
So if you're planning on doing that,
then just go to the next section.
But if you don't have the time,
or if you really want to focus only
on the most important parts and on your own learning goal,
then just keep watching.
So to help you navigate through this massive course
according to your goals,
I created a couple of different pathways through the course
and also a roadmap for each section.
So a section roadmap is basically an overview
of each section,
which will tell you exactly which videos
are the most important ones,
which ones are not that important,
and which ones are optional.
And you can find these roadmaps
at the beginning of each section.
And so by using them,
you can focus only on the most important videos if you want,
and therefore complete the course a lot faster.
So the section roadmaps tell you which videos you may skip.
But you might also want to skip entire sections.
So sections that you don't need to watch
in order to achieve your learning goal.
And so that's where the course pathways come into play.
So I defined these seven learning goals that you might have,
and selected the sections that you should watch
in order to achieve that goal.
And the seven pathways are any PDF document
that you can find right in the next lecture.
But just as an example here,
your goal might be to learn
only the most important parts of JavaScript.
And this might actually be a great goal
for Udemy for Business students,
who are probably watching this course at work.
Now, in this case, your pathway through the course
is gonna look something like this.
So just like in the section roadmaps,
here you can see which sections
are very important for your goal,
which ones are just good to know,
and which ones are optional.
And so again, by following a pathway like this,
you don't have to watch the entire course
if you don't have the time.
In fact, this particular pathway
actually shrinks the course down to only 24 hours.
All right.
So again, the best option is of course,
to watch the entire course from start to finish.
But if you don't have the time,
then please take a look at the course pathways PDF document
in the next lecture,
and select your learning goal and pathway from there.
And then I see you wherever your path
will take you in this course.
(upbeat music)